A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
After hearing reports of strange events in the Baltic Sea, Liz, Patty, and I set sail to investigate.
We found a survivor. He told us...
The Black Dragon came! The Black Dragon came and ate our village!
Shortly after that, we came upon a ship.
The Nidhogg was no normal vessel. It was a ghost ship, also known as the Black Dragon.
When we climbed aboard the ship, we found hundreds of disembodied human souls.
They were guarded by an evil spirit who refused to turn them over to us.
Nidhogg!
And then it appeared.
The demon sword, Ragnarok, which took the form of a Black Dragon.
Hey.
My blood is black, you know.
H.O.S.T.E.L.A.
H.O.S.T.E.R.
G.O.S.T.E.L.A.
you
Thank you.
I'm scared of everyone.
I need to learn to deal with people better.
But to do that, I need power.
Goofy.
Do you want to know where the real hell is hiding?
It's inside your head.
If you get in my way, I'll have to kill you, you know?
Will you?
Just try it.
Supreme domination through the attainment of ultimate power?
That's your genius plan for escaping from all your fear?
You disgust me.
If what you really want is to be free from fear, then strengthen your soul.
Always balance good and evil.
Did we get him?
You mean my attacks didn't stop that thing?
I guess I shouldn't expect you to understand me.
I shouldn't be surprised.
Not even the little one can understand me.
If the little one can't understand my feelings,
then there's no way a reaper like you could comprehend them.
Hey, Liz, does that thing?
Uh-huh.
It looks like us, Patty.
Back then.
Back before we became who we are now.
Patty.
Please, don't shoot me.
Hand over everything you've got.
Fine, I'll just take it from you then.
Get out of here!
We were born as weapons,
and we loved the power that came with it.
Nothing could scare us.
We walked around town like we owned the place,
taking whatever we wanted, whenever we wanted it.
No one ever thought to ask what our lives were really like.
That isn't what I meant, sis.
No, what I was asking was,
does that person look like a boy or girl?
Because I can't tell.
Huh?
Jeez, and you're always giving me a hard time about daydreaming.
That's what you meant?
Hey!
I'll show you!
What?
He's still alive?
Uh-oh.
This ship is my body,
and my body's this ship.
As long as the need hog stays afloat,
I'll never die.
You damn pretty fools!
You ate every last human soul uncollected!
You have no honor!
You've got zero respect for other people's property!
Let me teach you about honor!
Let's see how you'd like a little taste of my cannon!
Aim!
Aiming, sir!
Ready!
Ready, sir!
Okay!
Fire!
Huh?
How can you still be alive?
Damn, you are annoying.
What?
The demon sword's wavelength seems to be...
swelling.
I hate...
hate...
hate everyone!
But that's all right.
I can use my screams to blow them all away.
I bet dead people are a lot easier to get along with.
Pete!
No!
Blah!
Free apple!
No!
The captain split down the middle.
That sword is strong.
The ship isn't going to hold much longer.
I can't! The demon sword!
What now?
It's over now, little leaver boy.
Damn you! You're not getting away! Beelzebub!
I have to stop the Kishin.
No, no. I'm talking about the Kishin who's right next to you.
That's who I gathered these souls for.
What does that mean?
Is my father hiding something from me?
Listen carefully, Krona.
If the Reaper catches up with us, you won't be getting any dinner tonight, you got me?
Hey, no fair. I can't lose more weight. I don't know how to deal with being any skinnier than I already am.
Give it up!
Damn it!
The fog is lifting. I can see the sun again.
My guess is the ghost ship was causing the fog this whole time.
This isn't a great time for sunbathing!
Kid, what is it? Why did you decide to stop here all of a sudden? Shouldn't we get going?
Just look at it, Liz. Patti. Look at how the clouds are. Flowing right toward the sun.
It's so beautiful. Even the sky is symmetrical.
Seriously? You wacko.
This is truly amazing. Oh, how I love you. Symmetry!
Symmetry!
It's so invigorating. Oh, sun. Oh, clouds. I love you.
Hey, kids, snap out of it. What about the demon sword?
Damn it, I forgot. Did it get away?
Yeah, you let it escape.
Can you not understand the perfection of this moment?
All I understand is you're a perfect idiot.
Those heartless monsters. They took all the souls that I was going to offer to the Geishin.
Now I have to begin all over again.
Oh, great Geishin. Grant me one more chance to please you.
I have the results of your blood tests.
Okay. What do they say, doctor?
Your red and white cell counts are normal. I don't see any hemoglobin issues either.
It's good news. You're a very healthy young lady.
Huh? Really? Are you sure?
It's just that I'm certain I coughed up something.
Something.
It looked like black blood.
Why do you think that could be?
Well, over time blood tends to darken in color.
Maybe that's why the blood you coughed up looked black to you.
Yeah.
It's still kind of unsettling.
Unsettling.
Unsettling indeed.
I was there too, watching the whole thing.
I saw you cough up that black blood.
Such powerful resonance between weapon and Meister should cause the transfer of black blood.
Um, Dr. Medusa? Is something bothering you?
No, I was just deciding what medicine to give you.
Take one of these pills twice a day.
One in the morning and one at night.
These pills enhance the effects of black blood.
Maybe they can help to fix this new little glitch in my experiment.
So, Maka, how's Sol holding up these days?
What do you mean?
Is he still having that strange dream with the demon in it?
He seemed to be quite troubled by it.
What dream? What demon?
I'm sorry. I thought he would have told you about it. He told me.
Oh, yes, of course. That dream. I think it's all gone now.
He's doing fine, really.
What dream? Why didn't he tell me?
I'll kill Sol!
Is that all, Dr. Medusa?
Okay, well, thanks a lot. Bye-bye for now.
I'll see ya.
Such a stupid little girl.
He told her about it and he didn't tell me?
So basically, Sol feels he can trust Dr. Medusa more than he can trust his own partner.
That's it! He's got some explaining to do!
This doesn't make any sense. How has the black blood inside Maka disappeared?
The design of my experiment was flawless.
Maka. Maka Albarn, where is your file?
It's not here. Could somebody have taken it?
Is this what you're looking for, Doctor?
Oh, you startled me. I didn't see you standing there.
You shouldn't sneak up on people like that.
The partner's sole leader and Maka Albarn.
Why are you so interested in them?
What is this?
Well, it's just that those two have been through a lot lately, you know?
Can you explain what this is? I took it from Maka.
I must say, I've never come across this particular medicine before.
How much does he know?
Has the crazy professor figured out my real identity or is he just guessing?
Should I kill him?
It's a type of herbal remedy I created myself.
I designed it to improve blood circulation and help to regulate the pulse.
Ah.
I'm not even lying to him. Black blood works in much the same way that regular blood does.
The medicine will do exactly what I said it would.
Well, you caught me. I'm secretly obsessed with herbal remedies.
I know it seems strange. I mean, it is non-traditional medicine.
I just wanted to help Maka and soul, that's all.
How sweet of you, Doctor. That is quite endearing, really.
But tell me something. Are you helping because you're a doctor?
Or is it because you're a witch?
Shhh.
You're horrible commenting on my appearance like that. I don't have to listen to this from you. It's sexual harassment.
promise me something if you're gonna sue go after spirit first okay
if you broke that chair I hope you're going to pay for it
for a second there I think she wanted to kill me damn I'm shaking this is fear
that's good then I'd forgotten what it felt like
I guess the ball's in my court now
well Stein yes I'm certain of it
what about the location of Medusa's home already looked into it I was a very
meticulous man you know that hasn't changed we can handle this case
professor all right Sid Nygus just be careful we're dealing with a witch it's
not going to be easy trust me Stein we are aware of that we've seen plenty of
people lose their lives to witches during our time we'll take all the necessary
precautions let's go see it yeah we just need to find physical evidence that
she's a witch then Lord death can issue a warrant for we've seen the tip of the
treacherous serpent's tail and now now we have to grab it
Erica Erica I'm speaking to you through the snakes I implanted in your body look in the attache case there you'll find the item you need yes that one there that's it now go quickly
I assume I don't have to explain what you need to do next
I'm glad we're back that sure was a crazy trip huh
I'm pooped
Liz Patty you two go back home to Gallows Manor
where are you going kid I have to ask my father something
down there yeah you think you should I'm on it
I know that when I was alive I was a rather cautious man thank you very much
whoa this is supposed to be the home of a school nurse
look here a magic circle covered in witches writing
it's certain now
a diary yeah that's what it looks like to me
but I was not the type of man who went sneaking around reading women's diaries
this is no time for chivalry I think you can make an exception for a witch's diary
yeah I guess I can
huh
what it's all in here she knows everything about the academy
I think this could be showing us what Medusa is after and why she's been researching black blood
if she springs this plan during tomorrow's festivities we're in trouble we have to tell the professor and Lord death immediately
see
what the what are they
there
well I hope you enjoyed my tadpole bombs
ribbit I do like destroying things it's so lovely to have been born a witch
now I need to hurry up and get this to Medusa
well well hey ya long time no see kiddo good to have you back
I hear you ran into the demon sword
father I have something to ask you
oh
what's eating you kid
I may be a reaper but I'm still young and I understand that
still there is too much I don't know
someone mentioned the Kishan who is right next to us
what does that mean father
people and gods alike possess weaknesses
in order to bury those failings they seek strength and power
fear and desire are two sides of the same coin
no father
you're avoiding my question that's not what I'm asking you
the Kishan who's right next to us
I want you to explain that phrase to me
does it have something to do with why you can't leave the academy
I need to know father
tell me what it means
what it means
know
it's kind
How long are you waiting for us to wait for us?
If you want to grow up, it's a perfect style
As always, as you can see, as you can see,
as you can see, as you can see
神様いるなら聞いてよ
いついつまでもこの瞬間
リピートできない毎日を
見送らなくちゃだからあともう少しだけって
子供でいたい
Boys and Girls
何人もこのように隠れひそ
では夢を見ているっていうストーリー
あ、あ、あ、あ
盛が下がる
彼ら眠する
エビリット
ビ mungkin
繁が奏
テニum
…
ью
or some kind of hippo?
Excalibur!
I know, a Tasmanian devil!
No way.
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
Legend of the Holy Sword II,
want to go drinking, gambling, and playing?
Okay, let's all say it together.
You're lame!